[
    {
        "questionNo": "Q1",
        "question": "What is 0.37 same as?",
        "options": [
            "0.037",
            "0.307",
            "0.370",
            "0.0370"
        ],
        "correct": 2
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q2",
        "question": "In the decimal 0.789, what is the place value of 8?",
        "options": [
            "Tenths",
            "Hundredths",
            "Thousandths",
            "None of the above"
        ],
        "correct": 1
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q3",
        "question": "Which decimal is greater: 0.402 or 0.42?",
        "options": [
            "0.402",
            "0.42",
            "Both are equal",
            "Cannot be determined"
        ],
        "correct": 1
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q4",
        "question": "In the number 0.073, which digit is in the tenths place?",
        "options": [
            "0",
            "7",
            "3",
            "None"
        ],
        "correct": 0
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q5",
        "question": "In the decimal 0.2345, what is the place value of 4?",
        "options": [
            "Tenths",
            "Hundredths",
            "Thousandths",
            "Ten-thousandths"
        ],
        "correct": 2
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q6",
        "question": "Which of the following numbers is the smallest:<br> 0.809, 0.89, 0.8009, 0.8090?",
        "options": [
            "0.809",
            "0.89",
            "0.8009",
            "0.8090"
        ],
        "correct": 2
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q7",
        "question": "In the decimal 12.9875, what is the place value of 9?",
        "options": [
            "Tenths",
            "Hundredths",
            "Thousandths",
            "Ten-thousandths"
        ],
        "correct": 0
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q8",
        "question": "Arrange the following decimals in ascending order:<br> 0.501, 0.15, 0.510, 0.050.",
        "options": [
            "0.050, 0.15, 0.510, 0.501",
            "0.050, 0.15, 0.501, 0.510",
            "0.050, 0.501, 0.15, 0.510",
            "0.15, 0.050, 0.501, 0.510"
        ],
        "correct": 1
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q9",
        "question": "Which decimal number is the largest:<br> 0.123, 0.132, 0.213, 0.231?",
        "options": [
            "0.123",
            "0.132",
            "0.213",
            "0.231"
        ],
        "correct": 3
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q10",
        "question": "Arrange these decimals in ascending order:<br> 0.1, 0.01, 0.001, 1.0.",
        "options": [
            "0.001, 0.01, 0.1, 1.0",
            "0.1, 0.01, 0.001, 1.0",
            "1.0, 0.1, 0.01, 0.001",
            "0.01, 0.001, 0.1, 1.0"
        ],
        "correct": 0
    }
]
